Guide to the Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees: 1915-1985
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives, Cornell University Library
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees: 1915-1985
5488 B
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees.
669 linear feet.
Correspondence, Rule books, Agreements, etc.
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives, Cornell University Library
SUBJECTS
Names:
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees.
Subjects:
Railroads--Employees--Labor unions--United States--Sources.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Access Restrictions:
Restricted. Please contact the Kheel Center Reference Archivist for access information.
COLLECTION ARRANGEMENT
This forms a portion of collection #5488 B. The guide to the entire collection is available here.
Series CIV is arranged in 1 sub-series by Union file number.
Series CV is arranged in 344 sub-seires by Union file number.
CONTAINER LIST
- Series CIV. BROTHERHOOD 50TH ANNIVERSARY CELEBRATION
  - Sub-Series 507-0. Brotherhood 50th Anniversary Celebration
    - General, 1949 (Box 620, Folder 5)
      December 6-13, 1949.
    - General, 1949 (Box 620, Folder 6)
      November 30, 1949-December 5, 1949.
    - General, 1949 (Box 620, Folder 7)
      November 19-29, 1949.
    - General, 1949 (Box 620, Folder 8)
      September 1949-November 9, 1949.
    - General. Program, 1949 (Box 620, Folder 9)
      1949 December 29
    - General, 1949-1950 (Box 620, Folder 10)
      December 22, 1949-February 1950.
    - General, 1949 (Box 620, Folder 11)
      December 14-21, 1949.
    - General, 1949 (Box 620, Folder 12)
      November 10-18, 1949.
    - General. Record of Transactions of General Chairmen's Memorial Committee, 1949-1950 (Box 620, Folder 13)
    - General, 1950 (Box 620, Folder 14)
      March-May 1950.
    - General. Cincinnati, Ohio Festivities, 1949-1950 (Box 620, Folder 15)
- Series CV. 1951 CONVENTION RESOLUTIONS
  - Sub-Series 517-0. 1951 Convention Resolutions. General
    - General, 1951-1953 (Box 621a, Folder 1)
  - Sub-Series 517-1. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 1
    - Union representative to be paid on full-time basis by employer for policing contract, 1950-1951 (Box 621a, Folder 2)
  - Sub-Series 517-2. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 2
    - When Government takes over operation of any industry, it should also take over the revenues, 1951 (Box 621a, Folder 3)
  - Sub-Series 517-3. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 3
    - Amend Railway Labor Act to expedite handling of cases, 1951 (Box 621a, Folder 4)
  - Sub-Series 517-4. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 4
    - Amend Federal Employers' Liability Act, 1951-1956 (Box 621a, Folder 5)
  - Sub-Series 517-5. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 5
    - Endorse Bill H.R. 2945, Parcel Post Rates, 1951 (Box 621a, Folder 6)
  - Sub-Series 517-6. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 6
    - Amend Railway Labor Act to speed up negotiations thereunder, 1951 (Box 621a, Folder 7)
  - Sub-Series 517-7. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 7
    - Unfair competition of Parcel Post; appoint Express Committee to survey conditions in Express Industry and promote legislation to restrict, 1951 (Box 621a, Folder 8)
  - Sub-Series 517-8. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 8
    - Amend Railway Labor Act to provide that employer pay union representative for policing contract, 1951 (Box 621a, Folder 9)
  - Sub-Series 517-9. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 9
    - Amend Railway Labor Act to provide more expeditious handling of wage increase requests, 1951 (Box 621a, Folder 10)
  - Sub-Series 517-10. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 10
    - Amend Railway Labor Act to provide more expeditious handling of wage increase requests, 1951 (Box 621a, Folder 11)
  - Sub-Series 517-11. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 11
    - Endeavor to increase readers' interest in "Railway Clerk", 1951 (Box 621a, Folder 12)
  - Sub-Series 517-12. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 12
    - Strike benefits for our members when out of work because of work stoppages by other organizations., 1951 (Box 621a, Folder 13)
  - Sub-Series 517-13. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 13
    - Employees with 15 years' service to be allowed 15 working days' vacation, 1951 (Box 621a, Folder 14)
  - Sub-Series 517-14. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 14
    - Retirement at age 60 after 30 years' service, 1951 (Box 621a, Folder 15)
  - Sub-Series 517-15. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 15
    - Retirement at age 60 after 30 years' service; pension benefits to be increased 50%, 1951 (Box 621a, Folder 16)
  - Sub-Series 517-16. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 16
    - Liberalize benefits of Railroad Retirement Act, 1951 (Box 621a, Folder 17)
  - Sub-Series 517-17. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 17
    - Reduce retirement age to 60, 1951 (Box 621a, Folder 18)
  - Sub-Series 517-18. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 18
    - Extend wage increase escalator clause of Railroad Retirement Act to pensioners, 1951 (Box 621a, Folder 19)
  - Sub-Series 517-19. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 19
    - Retirement at age 60 after 30 years' service, 1951 (Box 621a, Folder 20)
  - Sub-Series 517-20. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 20
    - Amend Unemployment Insurance Act to increase sickness and unemployment benefits, 1951-1952 (Box 621a, Folder 21)
  - Sub-Series 517-21. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 21
    - Retirement after 30 years' service; annuity to be based on half of monthly wages of last 5 years, 1951 (Box 621a, Folder 22)
  - Sub-Series 517-22. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 22
    - Retirement with $150 per month minimum; optional retirement after 30 years' service or at age 60, 1951 (Box 621a, Folder 23)
  - Sub-Series 517-23. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 23
    - Amend Railroad Retirement Act to provide $100 per month minimum; reduce retirement age to 60; increase maximum deductions from $18 to $10 per month, 1951 (Box 621a, Folder 24)
  - Sub-Series 517-24. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 24
    - Retirement after 30 years' service with minimum of $150 per month, 1951 (Box 621a, Folder 25)
  - Sub-Series 517-25. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 25
    - Increase benefits of Railroad Retirement Act, 1951 (Box 621a, Folder 26)
  - Sub-Series 517-26. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 26
    - Retirement at age 60 after 30 years' service, 1951 (Box 621a, Folder 27)
  - Sub-Series 517-27. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 27
    - Amend Railroad Retirement Act to provide that all costs be paid by management, 1951 (Box 621a, Folder 28)
  - Sub-Series 517-28. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 28
    - Retirement after 30 years' service regardless of age, with $100 per month minimum, 1951 (Box 621a, Folder 29)
  - Sub-Series 517-29. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 29
    - Amend Unemployment Insurance Act to provide for increased benefits, 1951-1952 (Box 621a, Folder 30)
  - Sub-Series 517-30. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 30
    - Voluntary retirement after 30 years' service with $100 per month minimum, 1951 (Box 621a, Folder 31)
  - Sub-Series 517-31. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 31
    - Amend Unemployment Insurance Act to provide for liberalized benefits, 1951-1952 (Box 621a, Folder 32)
  - Sub-Series 517-32. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 32
    - Retirement after 30 years' service with full pension rights, 1951 (Box 621a, Folder 33)
  - Sub-Series 517-33. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 33
    - Retirement after 30 years' service regardless of age; reduce retirement age to 60, 1951 (Box 621a, Folder 34)
  - Sub-Series 517-34. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 34
    - Amend Railroad Retirement Act to provide more liberal benefits, 1951 (Box 621a, Folder 35)
  - Sub-Series 517-35. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 35
    - Expression of appreciation for work done by Grand Lodge, 1951 (Box 621a, Folder 36)
  - Sub-Series 517-36. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 36
    - Increase vacation allowances based on length of service, 1951 (Box 621a, Folder 37)
  - Sub-Series 517-37. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 37
    - Weekly paychecks, 1951 (Box 621a, Folder 38)
  - Sub-Series 517-38. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 38
    - Minimum 2 weeks' vacation; maximum 4 weeks, 1951 (Box 621a, Folder 39)
  - Sub-Series 517-39. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 39
    - Accident insurance for members injured while in service of the Brotherhood, 1951 (Box 621a, Folder 40)
  - Sub-Series 517-40. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 40
    - Payment for all legal holidays; 3 weeks' vacation after 15 years' service, 1951 (Box 621a, Folder 41)
  - Sub-Series 517-41. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 41
    - Weekly Pay Bill, 1951-1952 (Box 621a, Folder 42)
  - Sub-Series 517-42. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 42
    - Amend Railway Labor Act to prohibit discrimination against any employee because of race, color, or creed, 1951 (Box 621a, Folder 43)
  - Sub-Series 517-43. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 43
    - Amend National Vacation Agreement to provide more liberal vacations., 1951 (Box 621a, Folder 44)
  - Sub-Series 517-44. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 44
    - National Holiday Agreement, 1951-1952 (Box 621a, Folder 45)
  - Sub-Series 517-45. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 45
    - Advise status of grievances every 30 days, 1951 (Box 621a, Folder 46)
  - Sub-Series 517-46. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 46
    - 5 days' vacation after 1 year's service to 30 days' vacation after 20 years' service, 1951 (Box 621a, Folder 47)
  - Sub-Series 517-47. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 47
    - Good Friday Holiday, 1951 (Box 621a, Folder 48)
  - Sub-Series 517-48. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 48
    - Time and one-half to be paid for worked holidays, 1951 (Box 621a, Folder 49)
  - Sub-Series 517-49. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 49
    - Secure same free transportation rights and privileges for Railway Express Agency employees as enjoyed by railroad employees, 1951 (Box 621a, Folder 50)
  - Sub-Series 517-50. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 50
    - Liberalize vacation allowances, 1951 (Box 621a, Folder 51)
  - Sub-Series 517-51. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 51
    - Work week to be shortened as employee efficiency increases, 1951 (Box 621a, Folder 52)
  - Sub-Series 517-52. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 52
    - Brotherhood Lodges urged to affiliate with Central Labor Bodies of American Federation of Labor, 1951 (Box 621a, Folder 53)
  - Sub-Series 517-53. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 53
    - Amend National Vacation Agreement to provide more liberal vacations., 1951 (Box 621a, Folder 54)
  - Sub-Series 517-54. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 54
    - Negotiate National Holiday Agreement providing for 7 paid holidays each year, 1951 (Box 621a, Folder 55)
  - Sub-Series 517-55. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 55
    - Allow 3 foreign line free transportation passes annually, 1951 (Box 621a, Folder 56)
  - Sub-Series 517-56. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 56
    - Hospitalization and medical care, 1951 (Box 621a, Folder 57)
  - Sub-Series 517-57. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 57
    - 20 days' vacation after 20 years' service, 1951 (Box 621a, Folder 58)
  - Sub-Series 517-58. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 58
    - 10 days' vacation for 3 to 10 years' service; 1 additional day for each year thereafter with a maximum of 25 working days' vacation, 1951 (Box 621a, Folder 59)
  - Sub-Series 517-59. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 59
    - Revise Lehigh Valley Railroad Working Rules Agreement, 1951 (Box 621a, Folder 60)
  - Sub-Series 517-60. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 60
    - 15 days' vacation for 15 years' service; 1 additional day for each year thereafter with a maximum of 30 days, 1951 (Box 621a, Folder 61)
  - Sub-Series 517-61. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 61
    - Additional Protective Committee Division Chairman for Lodges with 175 or more members, 1951 (Box 621a, Folder 62)
  - Sub-Series 517-62. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 62
    - 12 days' vacation after 4 years' service to 30 days after 20 years, 1951 (Box 621a, Folder 63)
  - Sub-Series 517-63. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 63
    - Railway Express Agency over-the-road employees, 1951 (Box 621a, Folder 64)
  - Sub-Series 517-64. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 64
    - Unsafe, unfit Express cars, 1951 (Box 621a, Folder 65)
  - Sub-Series 517-65. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 65
    - Free transportation for Railway Express Agency employees, 1951 (Box 621a, Folder 66)
  - Sub-Series 517-66. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 66
    - Revise Express Messengers' Rules Agreement to provide not less than 12 working days' vacation with pay per month, 1951 (Box 621a, Folder 67)
  - Sub-Series 517-67. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 67
    - 12 days' vacation for 4 years to 30 days after 30 years, 1951 (Box 621a, Folder 68)
  - Sub-Series 517-68. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 68
    - Wage differentials for night work, 1951 (Box 621a, Folder 69)
  - Sub-Series 517-69. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 69
    - 3 weeks' paid vacation after 10 years, 1951 (Box 621a, Folder 70)
  - Sub-Series 517-70. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 70
    - Railway Express Agency employees to be paid for 7 legal holidays, 1951 (Box 621a, Folder 71)
  - Sub-Series 517-71. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 71
    - Wage differentials for night work, 1951 (Box 621a, Folder 72)
  - Sub-Series 517-72. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 72
    - Bulletining of supervisory positions., 1951 (Box 621a, Folder 73)
  - Sub-Series 517-73. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 73
    - 8-hour work guarantee for Express Messengers for any trip between established railroad terminals, 1951 (Box 621a, Folder 74)
  - Sub-Series 517-74. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 74
    - Express Messengers to be paid for all time at away-from-home terminal after 12 hours, 1951 (Box 621a, Folder 75)
  - Sub-Series 517-75. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 75
    - Express Messengers to be paid for all time in excess of 170 hours per month at time and one-half rate, 1951 (Box 621a, Folder 76)
  - Sub-Series 517-76. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 76
    - Liberalize vacation allowance for Express Messengers, 1951 (Box 621a, Folder 77)
  - Sub-Series 517-77. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 77
    - Liberalize free transportation allowances, 1951 (Box 621a, Folder 78)
  - Sub-Series 517-78. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 78
    - Liberalize vacation allowances, 1951 (Box 621a, Folder 79)
  - Sub-Series 517-79. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 79
    - Liberalize foreign line free transportation pass allowances, 1951 (Box 621a, Folder 80)
  - Sub-Series 517-80. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 80
    - 12 days' vacation after 4 years' service to 30 days for 30 years, 1951 (Box 621a, Folder 81)
  - Sub-Series 517-81. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 81
    - Equalize wage rates on similar positions in Railway Express Agency, 1951 (Box 621a, Folder 82)
  - Sub-Series 517-82. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 82
    - Revise Vacation Rule, Railway Express Agency, 1951 (Box 621a, Folder 83)
  - Sub-Series 517-83. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 83
    - Negotiate National Sick Leave Agreement, 1951 (Box 621a, Folder 84)
  - Sub-Series 517-84. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 84
    - Graduated vacation scale, 1951 (Box 621a, Folder 85)
  - Sub-Series 517-85. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 85
    - National Holiday and Sick Leave Agreement, 1951 (Box 621a, Folder 86)
  - Sub-Series 517-86. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 86
    - 9 and 12 days' vacation after 2 and 3 years' service, 1951 (Box 621a, Folder 87)
  - Sub-Series 517-87. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 87
    - 15 days' vacation after 5 years' service; 1 additional day for each year after 15 years' service, maximum 30 days, 1951 (Box 621a, Folder 88)
  - Sub-Series 517-88. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 88
    - Negotiate National Sick Leave Agreement, 1951 (Box 621a, Folder 89)
  - Sub-Series 517-89. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 89
    - Revise New York, New Haven and Hartford Railroad Agreement, 1951 (Box 621a, Folder 90)
  - Sub-Series 517-90. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 90
    - Negotiate National Holiday Agreement, 1951 (Box 621a, Folder 91)
  - Sub-Series 517-91. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 91
    - 15 days' vacation after 10 years' service, 1951 (Box 621a, Folder 92)
  - Sub-Series 517-92. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 92
    - Maximum of 15 days' vacation per year and 10 days' sick leave per year, 1951 (Box 621a, Folder 93)
  - Sub-Series 517-93. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 93
    - Payment of vacation time of deceased employee, due and not used, to widow or family of deceased, 1951 (Box 621a, Folder 94)
  - Sub-Series 517-94. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 94
    - Establish uniform wage scales, 1951 (Box 621a, Folder 95)
  - Sub-Series 517-95. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 95
    - Wage rates of Stores Department, Laborers, Janitors, Freight Handlers, etc. to receive upward adjustment, 1951 (Box 621a, Folder 96)
  - Sub-Series 517-96. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 96
    - Equalize wage rates and establish uniform wage scales, 1951 (Box 621a, Folder 97)
  - Sub-Series 517-97. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 97
    - 80% of employees to be assigned regular positions; free system transportation passes after 15 years' service, 1951 (Box 621a, Folder 98)
  - Sub-Series 517-98. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 98
    - Employees working between 6:00 pm and 7:00 am to receive 10% higher rate, 1951 (Box 621a, Folder 99)
  - Sub-Series 517-99. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 99
    - Organize and secure Agreement covering wages and working conditions on Canadian National Express, 1951 (Box 621a, Folder 100)
  - Sub-Series 517-100. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 100
    - 10 days' vacation for 1-5 years' service; 15 days for 5-10 years' service, 1951 (Box 621a, Folder 101)
  - Sub-Series 517-101. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 101
    - Paid holidays, 1951 (Box 621a, Folder 102)
  - Sub-Series 517-102. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 102
    - Liberalize free transportation pass privileges, 1951 (Box 621a, Folder 103)
  - Sub-Series 517-103. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 103
    - Status report on grievances every 30 days, 1951 (Box 621a, Folder 104)
  - Sub-Series 517-104. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 104
    - Amend National Vacation Agreement to provide payment of time and one-half if employee is required to work his scheduled vacation period, 1951 (Box 621a, Folder 105)
  - Sub-Series 517-105. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 105
    - Amend Section 8 of Vacation Agreement to provide payment of all earned vacation time upon death of employee, 1951 (Box 621a, Folder 106)
  - Sub-Series 517-106. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 106
    - Inaugurate national movement to incorporate free transportation pass rights into existing Agreements, 1951 (Box 621a, Folder 107)
  - Sub-Series 517-107. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 107
    - Grand President to render prompt replies and status reports on all pending cases, claims or grievances, 1951 (Box 621a, Folder 108)
  - Sub-Series 517-108. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 108
    - Status reports on grievances to be made to Local and Division Chairmen; no agreements or settlements to be made until they have concurrence of Local and Division Chairmen, 1951 (Box 621a, Folder 109)
  - Sub-Series 517-109. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 109
    - Utilization of Labor's manpower in economic and political planning and administration, 1951 (Box 621a, Folder 110)
  - Sub-Series 517-110. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 110
    - Amend Vacation Agreement to provide families of deceased employees vacation pay earned by deceased employee, 1951 (Box 621a, Folder 111)
  - Sub-Series 517-111. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 111
    - Complete Rules Agreement coverage of all groups represented by Brotherhood, 1951 (Box 621a, Folder 112)
  - Sub-Series 517-112. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 112
    - Amend Vacation Agreement to provide families of deceased employees vacation pay earned by deceased employee, 1951 (Box 621a, Folder 113)
  - Sub-Series 517-113. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 113
    - Ascertain reasons for the difference between number of free transportation passes granted by Western Lines and smaller number of passes granted by Eastern Lines and why passes are restricted on desirable trains, 1951 (Box 621a, Folder 114)
  - Sub-Series 517-114. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 114
    - Grand Lodge to advocate and promote more uniform interpretations and demand wholehearted cooperation from Local Lodges and System Board Grievance Committees, 1951 (Box 621a, Folder 115)
  - Sub-Series 517-115. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 115
    - National negotiations on vacation disputes, 1951 (Box 621a, Folder 116)
  - Sub-Series 517-116. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 116
    - 3 weeks' vacation with pay after 15 years' service, 1951 (Box 621a, Folder 117)
  - Sub-Series 517-117. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 117
    - Pay at rate of time and one-half in lieu of vacation not granted, 1951 (Box 621a, Folder 118)
  - Sub-Series 517-118. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 118
    - 5 days' vacation after 1 year's service to 15 days after 5 years; after 15 years 1 additional day for each year of service with a maximum of 30 days, 1951 (Box 621a, Folder 119)
  - Sub-Series 517-119. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 119
    - 15 and 20 days' vacation after 10 and 15 years' service, 1951 (Box 621a, Folder 120)
  - Sub-Series 517-120. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 120
    - Secure agreement guaranteeing full employment rights to all returning service veterans, 1951 (Box 621a, Folder 121)
  - Sub-Series 517-121. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 121
    - Negotiate National Sick Leave Agreement, 1951 (Box 621a, Folder 122)
  - Sub-Series 517-122. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 122
    - Rights of employees to free transportation to be fully restored, 1951 (Box 621a, Folder 123)
  - Sub-Series 517-123. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 123
    - Amend National Vacation Agreement to protect rights of employees temporarily dismissed, 1951 (Box 621a, Folder 124)